The Gods need a hero.
Immortals is a fantasy, action, drama film directed by Tarsem Singh.
Theseus is a mortal man chosen by Zeus to lead the fight against the ruthless King Hyperion,
who is on a rampage across Greece to obtain a weapon that can destroy humanity.
Theseus, played by Henry Cavill.
King Hyperion, played by Mickey Rourke.
Stavros, played by Stephen Dorff.
Phaedra, played by Freida Pinto.
Zeus, played by Luke Evans.
Old Zeus, played by John Hurt.
Immortals is a 2011 American epic fantasy action film directed by Tarsem Singh Dhandwar and starring Henry Cavill,
Stephen Dorff, Luke Evans, Isabel Lucas, John Hurt, Kellan Lutz, Freida Pinto, and Mickey Rourke.
Loosely based on the Greek myths of Theseus and the Minotaur, and the Titanomachy, the film was
previously named Dawn of War and War of the Gods before being renamed Immortals.
Principal photography began in Montreal on April 5, 2010.
Immortals premiered in Los Angeles on November 8 and was released in the
United States on November 11, 2011, by Relativity Media.
The film was a commercial success, grossing $227 million,
and received mixed reviews from critics.
The film explores themes of army, poison, mythology, zeus, sword fight.
The tone is emotional.